{
    "subject": "resource/Phillip_Goodhand-Tait",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kingston_upon_Hull",
    "human_readable": "Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Kingston upon Hull.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8971610069274902,
            "question": "Where was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80046546459198,
            "question": "What year was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7571028470993042,
            "question": "Who are some other notable people born in Kingston upon Hull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6917201280593872,
            "question": "What is significant about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6436409950256348,
            "question": "What is Phillip Goodhand-Tait known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6048513054847717,
            "question": "Are there any historical events related to Phillip Goodhand-Tait's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5415628552436829,
            "question": "Is there any other information about Phillip Goodhand-Tait?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47975584864616394,
            "question": "Where is Kingston upon Hull located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4200681447982788,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3192037045955658,
            "question": "Can you find any images or portraits of Phillip Goodhand-Tait?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Kingston upon Hull.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4209_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4209_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Kingston upon Hull located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4209_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information about Phillip Goodhand-Tait?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4209_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4209_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The birthplace of Phillip Goodhand-Tait is mentioned as \"Kingston upon Hull\" in multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4209/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4209/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Goodhand-Tait was born on January 3, 1945, in Kingston upon Hull,\" which supports the statement that Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Kingston upon Hull."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}